Edmund B. Chaffee Papers
Edmund B. Chaffee Papers
- Correspondence
  - 1921
    - Darr, John Whittier (Box 2)
    - Day, Jonathan (Box 2)
    - De Lavare, Marie (Box 2)
    - Dom - Don (Box 2)
    - Durant, Will (Box 2)
    - Easa - East (Box 2)
    - Eojar folks (Box 2)
    - Farber, B. F. - J. (Box 2)
    - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America (Box 2)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 3 folders (Box 2)
    - Fif - Fit (Box 2)
    - Floyd, Mr. and Mrs. William (Box 2)
    - Forbes, Mrs. Jesse (Box 2)
    - Fosdick, Harry Emerson (Box 2)
    - Freeman - Freeman, K. (Box 2)
    - Gellin, Francis (Box 2)
    - Goodwin, J. H. (Box 2)
    - Gordon, Dugald (Box 2)
    - Gre - Gro (Box 2)
    - Had - Hart (Box 2)
    - Harr - Hay (Box 2)
    - Hill Top Club (Box 2)
    - Holmes, John Haynes (Box 2)
    - Holmq - Hor (Box 2)
    - Hou - How (Box 2)
    - Hug - Hur (Box 2)
    - Ind - Int (Box 2)
    - Jaquith, Harold C. (Box 2)
    - Jenning, J. E. (Box 2)
    - Judd, Gertrude Brown (Box 2)
    - Kelsey, Mr. and Mrs. A. E. (Box 2)
    - Khosla, A. N. (Box 2)
    - Knight, Reverend Walter D. (Box 2)
    - Krell, David (Box 2)
    - Labor Temple
      - Affirmations, Notices of Church Services (Box 2)
      - Budget, Allocation of Funds, Finances (Box 2)
      - Contributions to, Appeals and Responses, Thank You Notes (Box 2)
      - Educational and Young People's Committee Meetings (Box 2)
      - Employment Inquiries and Recommendations (Box 2)
      - Maintenance and Repairs, Supplies, Equipment (Box 2)
      - Programs and Activities (Box 2)
      - Solicitations for Temple Business (Box 2)
      - Work Schedules and Instructions to Personnel (Box 2)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
    - League for Mutual Aid, The (Box 2)
    - Long, Cedric (Box 2)
    - Maclntosh, Mabel (Box 2)
    - McE - McK (Box 2)
    - Merr - Methe (Box 2)
    - Methodist-Episcopal Church Board of Home Missions (Box 2)
    - Mic - Min (Box 2)
    - Mosher, C. W. (Box 2)
    - Murphy, Albert John (Box 2)
    - Nas - Nat (Box 2)
    - Near East Relief (Box 2)
    - Needles, Cora (Box 2)
    - New York Cal - Cat (Box 2)
    - New York City
      - Department of Education - Police Department (Box 2)
      - Mission Society (Box 2)
      - Sunday School Association (Box 2)
    - New York Evening Post-Times (Box 2)
    - Newton, Ray (Box 2)
    - Nicol, Reverend James H. (Box 2)
    - Nolting, Edward L. (Box 2)
    - Outlook, The (Box 2)
    - Pai - Pat (Box 2)
    - Perkins, R. O. (Box 2)
    - Perlman, Nathan (congressman) (Box 2)
    - Pratt, I. Gentle (Box 2)
    - Presbyterian Church in the United States of America Board of Home Missions (Box 2)
    - Presbyterian Minister's Fund (Box 2)
    - Presbytery of New York
      - Church Extension Commission, 2 folders (Box 3)
      - Committee on Ministerial Relief and Sustenation (Box 3)
      - Forbes, J. F., Stated Clerk (Box 3)
    - Red - Rel (Box 3)
    - Richards, George H. (Box 3)
    - Ril - Riv (Box 3)
    - Roberts, Richard (Box 3)
    - Sachtleben, A. F. (Box 3)
    - Sayre, John Nevin (Box 3)
    - Scribner, Charles and Son (Box 3)
    - She - Shu (Box 3)
    - Simpson, William G. (Box 3)
    - Speers, Thomas Guthrie (Box 3)
    - Spring Street Neighborhood House (Box 3)
    - Ste - Str (Box 3)
    - Swartz, Charles B. (Box 3)
    - Thompson, Michael (Box 3)
    - Union Theological Seminary (Box 3)
    - United States Department of Labor, Immigration Commissioner F. A. Wallis (Box 3)
    - Vickerey, Charles (Box 3)
    - Villard, Oswald Garrison (Box 3)
    - Watson, Blanche (Box 3)
    - Web - Wes (Box 3)
    - White, Mrs. R. C. (Box 3)
    - Wil - Wit (Box 3)
    - Woo - Wor (Box 3)
    - Y.M.C.A. (Box 3)
    - Y.W.C.A. (Box 3)
    - Zimmer, A. (Box 3)
    - Unidentified (Box 3)
  - 1922
    - Academy of Political Science in the City of New York (Box 3)
    - American, Civil - Friends (Box 3)
    - Bai - Bar (Box 3)
    - Bergmann, Minnie (Box 3)
    - Bil - Bir (Box 3)
    - Bonamo, John and Marie (Box 3)
    - Brede, Alexander (Box 3)
    - Butler, Alicia (Box 3)
    - Chaffee, Family of (Box 3)
    - Christian Work, The (Box 3)
    - Civic Club of New York (Box 3)
    - Clarke, Merril F. (Box 3)
    - Coffin, Henry Sloane (Box 3)
    - Col - Con (Box 3)
    - Dav - Day (Box 3)
    - Dea - Den (Box 3)
    - Disciples Community House (Box 3)
    - Durant, Will (Box 3)
    - Eash - East (Box 3)
    - Farber, John Henry (Box 3)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 3 folders (Box 3)
    - Fin - Fit (Box 3)
    - Foo - For (Box 3)
    - Fosdick, Harry E. (Box 3)
    - Gordon, B. Gordon, Dugald (Box 3)
    - Gre - Gri (Box 3)
    - Haa - Har (Box 3)
    - Hat - Hay (Box 3)
    - Hillman, Sidney (Box 3)
    - Hillquit, Morris (Box 3)
    - Hor - How (Box 3)
    - Hunter, A. J. (Box 3)
    - Hygienic Laboratories (Box 3)
    - Jaquith, Harold C. (Box 3)
    - Kele - Kels (Box 3)
    - Labor Defense Council (Box 3)
    - Labor Temple
      - Committee Meetings, Notices and Responses Arranged for (Box 3)
      - Contributions, Appeals and Responses, Thank You Notes (Box 3)
      - Employment Inquiries and Recommendations (Box 3)
      - Maintenance and Repairs, Supplies, Equipment (Box 3)
      - Programs and Activities (Box 3)
      - Work Schedules and Instructions to Personnel (Box 3)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 3)
    - Land, Leon (Box 3)
    - Leagues for Industrial - Mutual (Box 3)
    - Mac C - May (Box 3)
    - McC - McL (Box 3)
    - Mea - Met (Box 3)
    - Mic - Mil (Box 3)
    - Mon - Mot (Box 3)
    - Musolino, Mary (Box 3)
    - Myers, James (Box 3)
    - Nan - Nar (Box 3)
    - Needles, C. Blanche (Box 3)
    - New York City Department of Health (Box 3)
    - New York Federation of Churches (Box 3)
    - New York L - T (Box 3)
    - Nicol, James H. (Box 3)
    - Nolting, Edward L. (Box 3)
    - Non - Noy (Box 3)
    - Page, Kirby (Box 3)
    - Pei - Par (Box 3)
    - Pfeiffer, Timothy (Box 3)
    - Presbyterian Minister's Fund (Box 3)
    - Presbytery of New York (Box 3)
    - Rel - Ret (Box 3)
    - Richards, George H. (Box 3)
    - Rivenburg, Narola (Box 3)
    - Sag - Say (Box 3)
    - Scarpaci, Frank (Box 3)
    - Seltzer, Thomas (Box 3)
    - Simpson, William (Box 3)
    - Sink, Senator Charles A. (Box 3)
    - Slater, F. M. (Box 4)
    - Smith, Shirley W. (Box 4)
    - Speers, Thomas Guthrie (Box 4)
    - Ste - Sto (Box 4)
    - Theta (Box 4)
    - Union Theological Seminary (Box 4)
    - Vedder, Beverley (Box 4)
    - Watk - Wats (Box 4)
    - Webber, Charles (Chuck) (Box 4)
    - Whita - Whitm (Box 4)
    - Wom - Wor (Box 4)
    - Yale University (Box 4)
    - Y.M.C.A. (Box 4)
    - Y.W.C.A. (Box 4)
    - Unidentified (Box 4)
  - 1923
    - Academy of Political Science (Box 4)
    - American, Board - Friends (Box 4)
    - Anti-Saloon League of New York (Box 4)
    - Baird, Dr. Addison W. (Box 4)
    - Berns, Albert (Box 4)
    - Bird, J. S. (Box 4)
    - Bowe, H. Eugene (Box 4)
    - Brede, Alexander (Box 4)
    - Buckley, Minnie A. (Box 4)
    - Cap - Cas (Box 4)
    - Chaffee, Family of January, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Chi - Chr (Box 4)
    - Civic Club of New York (Box 4)
    - Coffin, Henry Sloan (Box 4)
    - Col - Con (Box 4)
    - Durant, Will (Box 4)
    - Eastern Clergy Bureau (Box 4)
    - Edgar, M - S (Box 4)
    - Enc - End (Box 4)
    - Erie Railroad Company (Box 4)
    - Farber, Mr. and Mrs. (Box 4)
    - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Fellowship for a Christian Social Order (Box 4)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 4 folders (Box 4)
    - Fideles Club (Box 4)
    - Franco, Joseph (Box 4)
    - Gannett, Lewis S. (Box 4)
    - Gordon, Dugald (Box 4)
    - Har - Hay (Box 4)
    - Hillquit, Morris (Box 4)
    - Horton, Douglas (Box 4)
    - Hun - Hut (Box 4)
    - Jennings, H. R. (Box 4)
    - Joi - Jon (Box 4)
    - Kaliet, Isadore (Box 4)
    - Kee - Kel (Box 4)
    - King, Reverend G. Allen (Box 4)
    - LaMonte, Caroline (Box 4)
    - Labor Temple
      - Budget, Allocation of Funds, Finances (Box 4)
      - Committee Meetings, Notices and Responses, Arranged for (Box 4)
      - Contributions to, Appeals and Responses, Thank You Notes (Box 4)
      - Programs and Activities, 2 folders (Box 4)
      - Solicitations for Temple Business (Box 4)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 4)
    - League for Mutual Aid (Box 4)
    - Liberal, The (Box 4)
    - Lower New York Church League (Box 4)
    - Lyons, Rabbi Alexander (Box 4)
    - Mat - Mau (Box 4)
    - Merrill, William Pierson (Box 4)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church
      - Board of Home Missions and Church Extension (Box 4)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 4)
    - Mil - Min (Box 4)
    - Muste, A. J. (Box 4)
    - Nation - Nationa (Box 4)
    - New York Bible Society (Box 4)
    - New York City Mission Society (Box 4)
    - New York Federation of Churches (Box 4)
    - New York State Department of Comptroller - Tax (Box 4)
    - New York Stomatological Society (Box 4)
    - Nicol, James H. (Box 4)
    - Niebuhr, Reinhold (Box 4)
    - Nipps, J. W. (Box 4)
    - Nolting, Edward L. (Box 4)
    - Pool, David De Sola (Box 4)
    - Presbyterian Church in the United States of America
      - Board of Home Missions (Box 4)
      - Board of National Missions (Box 4)
      - Synod of New York (Box 4)
    - Presbytery of New York
      - Church Extension Committee, Savage, Theodore F., Secretary (Box 4)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 4)
    - Randolph, A. Philip (Box 5)
    - Restucci Family (Box 5)
    - Richards, George H. (Box 5)
    - Rochester, Anna (Box 5)
    - Sayre, John Nevin (Box 5)
    - Speers, Thomas Guthrie (Box 5)
    - Teller, Chester Thomas, Norman (Box 5)
    - Union Theological Seminary (Box 5)
    - United States Shipping Board Emergency Fleet Corporation (Box 5)
    - United States, The White House (Box 5)
    - Vermont, State of, re: Houses for Sale (Box 5)
    - Wai - Wal (Box 5)
    - War Resisters' League (Box 5)
    - Williams - Williamsb (Box 5)
    - Women's Peace Society - Union (Box 5)
    - Wood, Clement (Box 5)
    - Work - Worl (Box 5)
    - Y.M.C.A. (Box 5)
    - Y.W.C.A., 2 folders (Box 5)
  - 1924
    - Academy Press (Box 5)
    - American Association - Parish (Box 5)
    - Arb - Art (Box 5)
    - Bai - Bak (Box 5)
    - Berg - Bern (Box 5)
    - Big - Bir (Box 5)
    - Bond, Grace E. (Box 5)
    - Brooklyn Jewish Center, The (Box 5)
    - Can - Cas (Box 5)
    - Chaffee, Family of (Box 5)
    - Christian - Jewish Fellowship (Box 5)
    - Civic - Civil (Box 5)
    - Coffin, Henry Sloan (Box 5)
    - Com - Coo (Box 5)
    - Copeland, Senator Royal S. (Box 5)
    - Crapullo, George A. (Box 5)
    - Darby, Hooper and McDaniel (Box 5)
    - Davis, Jerome (Box 5)
    - Day, C - S (Box 5)
    - Delta Sigma Rho (Box 5)
    - Dol - Dor (Box 5)
    - Du Bois, Paul (Box 5)
    - Durant, Will (Box 5)
    - Eddy, Sherwood (Box 5)
    - Eller, A. D. (Box 5)
    - Eugenics Committee of the United States (Box 5)
    - Evans, H. G. (Box 5)
    - Federal - Federat (Box 5)
    - Fellowship for Christian Social Order (Box 5)
    - Fellowship of Faiths (Box 5)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation (Box 5)
    - Foote, Mrs. E. M. (Box 5)
    - Fosdick, Harry Emerson (Box 5)
    - Fowler, Doris (Box 5)
    - Fraternity for Friendly Service (Box 5)
    - Gannett, Lewis S. (Box 5)
    - Garman, Roy (Box 5)
    - Gie - Gil (Box 5)
    - Gordon, Dugald (Box 5)
    - Greater New York Federation of Churches, The (Box 5)
    - Hard - Harl (Box 5)
    - Hart - Hat (Box 5)
    - Hill, Clifford (Box 5)
    - Hillman, Sidney (Box 5)
    - Hitchcock, William Foster (Box 5)
    - Holly High School Alumni (Box 5)
    - Holmes, John Haynes (Box 5)
    - Hop - Hor (Box 5)
    - Hum - Hun (Box 5)
    - International Association of Daily Vocational Bible Schools (Box 5)
    - Iowa State Traveling Men's Association (Box 5)
    - Jaquith, Harold C. (Box 5)
    - Johnson, Charles (Box 5)
    - Kelsey, A. Edward and Marion (Box 5)
    - Kilborne, Reverend T. T. (Box 5)
    - Klein, Reverend W. E. (Box 5)
    - Knopf, Alfred A. (Box 5)
    - Labor D - M (Box 5)
    - Labor Temple
      - Annual Reports, Statements, Audits (Box 5)
      - Budget, Allocation of Funds, Finances (Box 5)
      - Committee Meetings, Notices and Responses Arranged for (Box 5)
      - Employment Inquiries and Recommendations (Box 5)
      - Programs and Activities, 3 folders (Box 5)
      - Solicitations for Temple Business (Box 5)
      - Work Schedules and Instructions to Personnel (Box 5)
    - Landy Brothers Music House (Box 5)
    - Lea - Lev (Box 5)
    - Liberal - Listener (Box 6)
    - McAll, R. L. (Box 6)
    - Mil - Min (Box 6)
    - Mothershill, Rolland V. (Box 6)
    - Muste, A. J. (Box 6)
    - National Association for Church Development (Box 6)
    - National Conference on the Christian Way of Life, 3 folders (Box 6)
    - National S - Natu (Box 6)
    - Needles, C. Blanche (Box 6)
    - New York American (Box 6)
    - New York City
      - Board of Education (Box 6)
      - Mission Society (Box 6)
    - New York Governor, Smith, Alfred E (Box 6)
    - New York State Board of Charities (Box 6)
    - Niebuhr, Reinhold (Box 6)
    - Nolting, Ed (Box 6)
    - Odvin Brothers (Box 6)
    - Page, Kirby (Box 6)
    - Palisades Interstate Park, Commissioners of (Box 6)
    - Penguins Club, The (Box 6)
    - Pratt and McAlpin (Merle-Smith) (Box 6)
    - Presbyterian Church in the United States of America (Box 6)
    - Presbytery of New York
      - Church Extension Committee, Savage, Theodore - Secretary (Box 6)
      - Evangelistic Committee (Box 6)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 6)
    - Provincetown Playhouse (Box 6)
    - Rathburn, Alan (Box 6)
    - Rec - Rei (Box 6)
    - Richards, E. (Box 6)
    - Richards, George H. (Box 6)
    - Roth, Emory (Box 6)
    - Salmon, Ellen (Box 6)
    - Sch - Sco (Box 6)
    - Sea - Sel (Box 6)
    - Sim - Sip (Box 6)
    - Socialist Labor Party, The (Box 6)
    - Speers, Guthrie (Box 6)
    - Ste - Stu (Box 6)
    - Sumner, John S. (Box 6)
    - Teacher's Union Auxiliary (Box 6)
    - Theta (Box 6)
    - Thomas, Norman (Box 6)
    - Timper, Mrs. A. (Box 6)
    - Union Theological Seminary (Box 6)
    - United States, Government of, re: War (Box 6)
    - Ver - Ves (Box 6)
    - Villard, Oswald Garrison (Box 6)
    - Wadsworth, James W. (congressman) (Box 6)
    - Walser, Jean (Box 6)
    - Web - Wei (Box 6)
    - Wilb - Will (Box 6)
    - Wise, Stephen S. (Box 6)
    - Wom - Wor (Box 6)
    - X A (Box 6)
    - Young, Thomas H. (Box 6)
    - Y.M.C.A. (Box 6)
    - Y.W.C.A., 3 folders (Box 6)
    - Zito, George and Anthony (Box 6)
    - Unidentified (Box 6)
  - 1925
    - Acq - Act (Box 6)
    - Ale - All (Box 6)
    - American
      - Birth - Committee (Box 6)
      - Farm - Seam (Box 6)
      - Seat - Stomatological Society (Box 6)
    - Anderson, Reverend S. R. (Box 6)
    - Appasamy, K. (Box 6)
    - Ara - Arn (Box 6)
    - Atkinson, Henry A. (Church Peace Union) (Box 6)
    - Baj - Bap (Box 6)
    - Barr - Bart (Box 6)
    - Beardsley, Lyndon (Box 6)
    - Blood, John W. (Box 6)
    - Boy Rangers of America (Box 6)
    - Bra - Bron (Box 6)
    - Brooklyn Society for Ethical Culture (Box 6)
    - Brow - Bry (Box 6)
    - Cadman, S. Parkes (Box 6)
    - Carter, E. C. (Box 6)
    - Chaffee, Family of, 4 folders (Box 6)
    - Cham - Chu (Box 6)
    - Citi - City (Box 6)
    - Civic Club of Carlisle (Pennsylvania) (Box 6)
    - Civic Club, The (New York City) (Box 6)
    - Clarke, Merrill Fowler (Box 6)
    - Coffin, Henry Sloane (Box 6)
    - Com - Con (Box 6)
    - Cooper, Elizabeth (Box 6)
    - Dailey, Granville P. (Box 6)
    - Davis, Jerome (Box 6)
    - Day, Jonathan C. (Box 7)
    - Dod - Don (Box 7)
    - Dud - Duf (Box 7)
    - Durant, Will, 6 folders (Box 7)
    - Durgin, Chester (Box 7)
    - Eastern Clergy Bureau (Box 7)
    - Edgar, Samuel (Box 7)
    - Eva - Eve (Box 7)
    - Fag - Far (Box 7)
    - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Fellowship of Faiths, 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation (Box 7)
    - Fif - Fin (Box 7)
    - Flanagan, Albert (Box 7)
    - Foreign Language Information Service (Box 7)
    - Fosdick, Harry Emerson (Box 7)
    - Fowler, Frederick (Box 7)
    - Fra - Fri (Box 7)
    - Gen - Ger (Box 7)
    - Gillies, Florence A. (Box 7)
    - Gordon, Dugald (Box 7)
    - Greene, Amy and Theodore (Box 7)
    - Hamilton, George (Box 7)
    - Harkness, Edward S. (Box 7)
    - Harr - Hart (Box 7)
    - Heckscher, August (Box 7)
    - Hepner, Joseph (Box 7)
    - Hill, Clifford (Box 7)
    - Holmes, John Haynes, 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Holmes, Richard S. (Box 7)
    - Hoo - Hop (Box 7)
    - Hor - Hoy (Box 7)
    - Hunter, Graham (Box 7)
    - Hymn Society, The (Box 7)
    - Imes, William (Box 7)
    - Industrial Pioneer (Box 7)
    - Italian-American Artistic League, The (Box 7)
    - Jaquith, Harold C. (Box 7)
    - Johnson, E. L. (Box 7)
    - Kasherman, Bessie (Box 7)
    - Kel - Ket (Box 7)
    - Knight, Walter David (Box 7)
    - Kurnvilla, K. K. (Box 7)
    - Labor Temple
      - Affirmations, Notices of Church Services (Box 7)
      - Annual Reports, Statements, Audits (Box 7)
      - Budget, Allocation of Funds, Finances (Box 7)
      - Committee Meetings, Notices and Responses Arranged for (Box 7)
      - Contributions to, Appeals and Responses, Thank You Notes, 2 folders (Box 7)
      - Employment Inquiries and Recommendations, 7 folders (Box 7)
      - Maintenance and Repairs, Supplies, Equipment, etc., 6 folders (Box 7)
      - Programs and Activities, 5 folders (Box 7)
      - Work Schedules, Instructions to Personnel, 5 folders (Box 7)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 7)
    - Labor Temple, East 84th Street (Box 7)
    - Lai - Las (Box 7)
    - League for Industrial Democracy (Box 7)
    - League, Abolition - Neighbors (Box 7)
    - Lib - Lis (Box 7)
    - Loria, Anthony (Box 7)
    - MacK - May (Box 7)
    - Mc A - Mc C (Box 7)
    - McG - McQ (Box 8)
    - Mer - Met (Box 8)
    - Miller C - R (Box 8)
    - Moh - Mow (Box 8)
    - National A - C (Box 8)
    - National F - U (Box 8)
    - Near - New York A (Box 8)
    - New York City Departments of Health and Public Welfare (Box 8)
    - New York State Board of Charities (Box 8)
    - New York T - U (Box 8)
    - Nicol, James H. (Box 8)
    - Nolting, Ed - Non Partisan Committee for the Election of Norman Thomas (Box 8)
    - O'Brien, Daniel (Box 8)
    - Opportunity (Box 8)
    - Pal - Pat (Box 8)
    - Per - Pet (Box 8)
    - Pfaffli, Marguerite (Box 8)
    - Phelps, Grace (Box 8)
    - Pillsbury, Mr. and Mrs. George (Box 8)
    - Pioneer Youth of America, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Pollock, Channing (Box 8)
    - Powys, John Cowper (Box 8)
    - Presbyterian Church in the United States of America
      - Board of Christian Education (Box 8)
      - Board of National Missions, 3 folders (Box 8)
      - Social Commission of 1925 (Box 8)
    - Presbytery of New York, Church Extension Committee
      - Merle-Smith, Treasurer (Box 8)
      - Savage, Theodore F., Secretary, 3 folders (Box 8)
      - Mendenhall, H. G., Stated Clerk (Box 8)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
    - Quill Club, The (Box 8)
    - Ram - Rat (Box 8)
    - Reconciliation Trips (Box 8)
    - Red - Ret (Box 8)
    - Richards, Edward (Box 8)
    - Richards, George H., 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Rick - Riv (Box 8)
    - Rogers Peet Company (Box 8)
    - Roth, Emery, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Russe - Russi (Box 8)
    - Rybicki, Edward C. (Box 8)
    - Sai - Sap (Box 8)
    - Saw - Say (Box 8)
    - Schneider, Albin F. (Box 8)
    - Sevenoak, F. L. (Box 8)
    - Shapleigh, Elisabeth (Box 8)
    - Sim - Sip (Box 8)
    - Slater, F. M. (Box 8)
    - Sme - Smi (Box 8)
    - Socialist Party, Italian Socialist Branch (Box 8)
    - Speers, Thomas Guthrie, 3 folders (Box 8)
    - Spi - Spr (Box 8)
    - Sta - Str (Box 8)
    - Thomas, Norman (Box 8)
    - Underwood and Underwood Studios (Box 8)
    - Union Theological Seminary (Box 8)
    - United H - N (Box 8)
    - Val - Van (Box 8)
    - Voorhis, Therese (Box 8)
    - Waid, D. Everett (Box 8)
    - Wal - Wat (Box 8)
    - Web - Wes (Box 8)
    - Wilb - Wils (Box 8)
    - Wise, Stephen S. (Box 8)
    - Women's I - T (Box 8)
    - Work - Worl (Box 8)
    - Wray, Elizabeth (Box 8)
    - Wylee, W. (Box 8)
    - Yergin, Howard (Box 8)
    - Y.M.C.A., 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Y.W.C.A., 3 folders (Box 8)
    - To and From Others (Box 8)
  - 1926
    - Alb - All (Box 8)
    - American A - F (Box 8)
    - American P - T (Box 8)
    - Arb - Arg (Box 8)
    - Association of Volunteers in Social Service (Box 8)
    - Atlas Iron Workers, Inc. (Box 8)
    - Avery, C. L. (Box 8)
    - Bab - Bat (Box 8)
    - Bea - Bec (Box 9)
    - Ben - Ber (Box 9)
    - Bon - Bow (Box 9)
    - Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters (Box 9)
    - Bun - Bur (Box 9)
    - Cai - Cam (Box 9)
    - Chaffee, Family of, 4 folders (Box 9)
    - Char - Chi (Box 9)
    - Christian Century Press, The (Box 9)
    - Christian-Jewish Fellowship, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Christian Work (Box 9)
    - Civic Club, The (Box 9)
    - Clar - Clas (Box 9)
    - Coffin, Henry Sloan (Box 9)
    - Col - Con (Box 9)
    - Copeland, Senator Royal S. (Box 9)
    - Council of W - on I (Box 9)
    - Crandon, L. R. G. (Box 9)
    - Dai - Day (Box 9)
    - De Witt G - T (Box 9)
    - Dob - Dom (Box 9)
    - Dud - Dun (Box 9)
    - Durant, Will, 4 folders (Box 9)
    - Eastern Clergy Bureau (Box 9)
    - Emergency Committee on Strikers' Relief (Box 9)
    - Emmons, J. T. (Box 9)
    - Erikson, John (Box 9)
    - Everett, Mrs. E., 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Fag - Far (Box 9)
    - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America (Box 9)
    - Feiker, Mr. and Mrs. George E. (Box 9)
    - Fellowship of Faiths (Box 9)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation (Box 9)
    - Fisk University (Box 9)
    - Flans, H. Ford, Prentice (Box 9)
    - Fosdick, Harry Emerson (Box 9)
    - Foster, Helen H. (Box 9)
    - Fra - Free (Box 9)
    - Fren - Fri (Box 9)
    - Garrigues, Mrs. E. B. (Box 9)
    - General Defense Committee (Box 9)
    - Gillies, Florence (Box 9)
    - Gordon, Dugald (Box 9)
    - Gra - Gre (Box 9)
    - Harrington, Barr (Box 9)
    - Hartford Theological Seminary (Box 9)
    - Hatch, Harold (Box 9)
    - Hea - Hes (Box 9)
    - Hill, Clifford S. (Box 9)
    - Hillquit, Morris (Box 9)
    - Hirst, Dr. V. B. (Box 9)
    - Holmes, John Haynes (Box 9)
    - Holmes, Richard S. (Box 9)
    - Hop - Hou (Box 9)
    - Hum - Hun (Box 9)
    - Imes, William Lloyd (Box 9)
    - Ind - Inw (Box 9)
    - Iowa State Traveling Men's Insurance (Box 9)
    - Jae - Jaq (Box 9)
    - Jelliffe, W. R. (Box 9)
    - Joh - Join (Box 9)
    - Kelsey, Mr. and Mrs. Edward (Box 9)
    - Khan, William B. (Box 9)
    - King, C - G (Box 9)
    - Kling, Phina (Box 9)
    - Knight, Walter David (Box 9)
    - Koukol, Alois (Box 9)
    - L. T. Building Corporation (Box 9)
    - Labor Temple
      - Budget, Allocation of Funds, Finances (Box 9)
      - Committee Meetings, Notices and Responses, Arranged for (Box 9)
      - Contributions to, Appeals and Responses, Thank You Notes, 2 folders (Box 9)
      - Employment Inquiries and Recommendations, 3 folders (Box 9)
      - Maintenance and Repairs, Supplies and Equipment, 4 folders (Box 9)
      - Programs and Activities January, February, 2 folders (Box 9)
      - Programs and Activities March-December, 7 folders (Box 10)
      - Solicitations for Labor Temple Business (Box 10)
      - Work Schedules and Instructions to Personnel, 4 folders (Box 10)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
    - Lasker, Bruno (Box 10)
    - League for Age Security, 3 folders (Box 10)
    - League for A - M (Box 10)
    - Lem - Li (Box 10)
    - Lower East Side Community Council (Box 10)
    - Mad - Mar (Box 10)
    - Mc A - Mc K (Box 10)
    - Mer - Met (Box 10)
    - Moo - Mot (Box 10)
    - Muste, A. J. (Box 10)